[INTRO] If you don't actively lead...
[INTRO] The pelvis can be loosened if you...
[INTRO] If you can't make angulation well, when you ride on a step slope...
[INTRO] You can never take the expert slope like that...
Hi. I am Seung Won Kim.
Now, we are going to practice the Angulation today. ("oegyeong" in korean)
Angulation is what many people already know
It is a technique to make a higher edge angle on the same central axis.
Well, to put it simply,
we generally refer to lifting the upper body
in the opposite direction of the slope while it's tilted.
In English, it is called angulation.
It's also called a the Lean-Out.
The nuances may be a little different
In general, it is used in the same sense.
By the way, those who have learned a lot or watched a lot of videos
usually practice down first after doing basic carving in general.
I think it would be nice to explain why I practice the Angulation first.
Of course, it's not wrong to practice down first.
When I show you Angulation,
I'll practice in a high BBP position with only a little down.
If you practice down, you usually overdo it during practice,
but if you keep on practicing,
your pelvic rotation or basic posture often collapses.
There are many cases where basic postures collapses.
So the down practice might be done well,
but when you try to practice the angulation later on,
the balance of the pelvic rotation is broken,
so there are many cases where Angulation practice does not work properly.
Especially there are a lot of cases that the hip often protrude in the toe side turn,
LG: don't we want the hip to protrude do the side?
or the pelvic rotation is not good in the heel side turn,
so it often happens due to the forward shifted weight.
So in my case, my personal know-how
indicates to minimize down and practice the angulation first.
And since most of the videos that come up are in one-point-lesson format,
despite the fact that some people teach you to down them (without mentioning the angulation),
There are a lot of cases where the angulation is already used while down.
In fact, when beginners practice,
it's not easy to down with the anguation.
Of course, some people with good athletic ability may follow along well,
but my experience is that there are more people who don't.
So for those of you who can't do it well,
you should practice the angulation first
and then try using a method that slowly increases the down.
For someone who practiced down first,
if you thought, "It's not good for the angulation,"
Don't try to give down too hard
minimize down, practice the angulation first,
Now, let's stand up and figure out how to use Angulation.
And I'll explain how to practice Angulation.
Thank you
Now then,
I'll show you how to do Angulation.
I've explained the basic BBP posture in Angulation before.
Among the BBP positions, you can take a high BBP posture.
The high BBP position is to lean very slightly against the rear boot,
the front leg are stretched out as much as possible,
and the upper body is a little bit bent,
take a high position.
And raise your arms slightly forward.
It would be nice to assume that the hand is approximately located on the top of the front boot.
Because when you give an angulation later, you'll see the position of this hand towards the front boot.
you'll see that the position of this hand goes this way towards the front boot,
and you can check if you're leaning forward or if your pelvis rotates properly,
so I recommend you to put your hand on the top of the front boot like this.
Let me show you the heel-turn.
In the case of heel-turn, you would have positioned your upper body like this when you did basic carving,
but when you do the angulation this time,
you would feel like you're moving over the left hip of your pelvis.
Like this.
If you ride it like this, you might feel like, "Doesn't my hip stick out too much?"
But it never does.
It's okay for your hip to stick out,
so don't tilt your upper body first,
but with your legs barely bent,
you should move on like your pelvis is falling out before upper body.
You'd better keep your shoulder line parallel to the slope when you move on.
In reality you may not level the arms properly,
so if possible, raise your outer arm a little too high.
You can make a more effective turn if you ride it with more arms than the parallel one.
Assume your left arm lifted when the heel turn went in,
doing the pelvic rotation, ride like this (demonstration)
When you're riding like this, like I said earlier,
it would be nice if you could check yourself to see if your right arm goes up the front boot.
As I explained earlier, if the pelvic rotation doesn't work properly,
when you incline,
You can see that your right arm isn't over your front boot,
you should't get it over your rear boot, or, in somewhere the middle.
Make it exactly over your front boot.
Then you know:
"I'm not doing my pelvic rotation right."
And I'll show you a toe-turn.
In case of toe-turns, it's also in a high BBP position.
You should take a high BBP posture and move like this.
This is the same thing.
When you move on, you shouldn't move like this.
There's a lot of people riding like this.
It's not the head is going over
The upper body stays still with a feeling of pelvis sticking out.
You need to make the Inclination as if your pelvis is going over your center of gravity.
(As I was editing the video I noticed,
when I'm doing this Angulation pose,
it may look like my rear leg is stretching out.
Absolutely not.
As I explained earlier,
the high BBP posture is slightly leaning on the rear leg of the boots.
If you want to stretch your legs like this and take Angulation,
It's a lot more difficult and uncomfortable.
Take high BBP posture, leaning lightly on your boots.
Push your pelvis in like this.
Please pay attention to this part.)
The shoulders are also going to be parallel to the slope.
Okay, the pelvis goes over first. Angulation.
The same goes for the toe-turn Angulation,
and the right arm is raised,
and the left arm is raised above the front boot.
Now, Angulation.
If you look at it at first, the Angulation position seems to be unstable.
Something like this... You may experience pelvis shaking,
it's because you are not used to the balance of riding with angulation yet.
I think you'll get better when they practice.
Now, I'd like to emphasize this, too.
If you think your pelvis is shaking like this,
you are pushing the pelvis correctly,
but you should do it more bold,
if you put in a lot more, the shaking will disappear.
Think, "I still don't have enough pelvis.".
You can push your pelvis more aggressively towards the slope,
and you'll be able to solve the problem.
Try practicing like that.
Now, I'd like to give you one more tip.
When you do the heel-turn,
you use a rotation very little in the carving in generally,
but if you don't give any rotation when you tilt body in the heel-turn,
as I said the basic carving before,
during the turn, the direction of the turn and the pelvic rotation are the same as,
so if you don't actively lead,
your pelvis can be loosened.
So, even if you first go in with your hands over the front boot like this well,
it's not moving much actually,
but in your mind as if I'm leading a deck into my upper body,
I think leading the upper body like this
can be a good tip to keep the pelvis from loosening.
I'll show you the carving using Angulation.
As I told you before,
take a high BBP posture using pelvic rotation.
Then, lift your arms slightly forward, so that they can be positioned at your front boot.
And, as you turn around, the heel-turn lifts your left shoulder.
The toe-turn raises the right shoulder and aligns it parallel to the slope.
You just have to look in the natural direction.
In the case of the heel-turn, the upper body rotation... Instead of a top body rotation,
you need to do a heel-turn to feel like you're leading the upper body
so that your pelvis won't loosen up a lot.
Okay. I'll show you.
Toe
Heel
Now, let's lead lightly.
Toe
Heel
Now, as you can see,
It's very important to practice with only angulation,
while keeping your upper body up a bit higher,
without bending your knees too much.
Now look again
The shoulder line raises the shoulder as if it is aligned with the slope.
Heelside
Raise your left shoulder.
I don't do much down yet.
Now toe side.
Now Heelside.
If you get used to it,
you can make more edges.
Like this.
The angulation is much more important in toe-turn than heel-turn.
But I can't really see the toe-turn Angulation in the video I took.
I think it's because I try to ride purely Angulation
instead of using advanced techniques like counter-rotation.
I guess I can't really see it because I'm filming from the back.
So I'm going to show you a little bit more about the Angulation
while watching the video I took three seasons ago.
Now, this is a video I took three seasons ago.
When you enter the toe-turn,
like I said before,
It's not that your head is falling.
Rather push your pelvis towards the slope.
Like this.
I do it.
When you see a lot of beginners riding,
there aren't many people who ride it like this.
But if you don't lose by pushing your pelvis in and giving you
angulation, when you get on a slope with a steep slope. Never!
LG: this sentence still makes little sense
Without using Angulation, regardless of the quality of the turn,
ff you ride in such a position as your hip rise to the sky,
and your head goes to the ground,
you will never ride the expert slope.
I would like to explain the physical reasons for this.
I'll teach you a theory later with only detailed Angulation.
First of all, it's important to have a different feeling of pushing your pelvis towards the ground.
I think it'd be nice if you could watch this video and try copying it.
Because this video is not purely Angulation
when pushing toe-turn Angulation,
your left arm's position will be farther behind than the front binding.
LG: will it be? if you don't do counterrotation ?
This is a bit of a technique called counter rotation.
Don't worry much about this part
Also, don't try to do this right now
First, push your pelvis towards the slope
Heads up!
Shoulders stay parallel!
It's important that you ride with that image.
So, I hope you don't care too much about that
And I'm not going to look at the direction of travel.
as we've learned,
When we're edge-changing,
I'm going to look at the fall line a little bit sooner.
I'll explain this in more detail later.
Don't copy this.
If you copy this, you'll slip and the turn won't work.
So, there are things you need to learn after the turn is somewhat stable.
And there are things you need to know at the beginner level.
First of all, I really hope you focus on the things I've told you and get on.
Please don't do this now. Please.
Now, the basic carving is the same,
If you can't make angulation well,
you can practice it with side-slip in the steep section.
As I mentioned in Basic Carving,
the condition in which this edge stands on one side is very similar
to that in the case of basic carving or carving using Angulation.
So, if you give me an Angulation at the side-slip stage,
you'll get a lot of help when you ride with Angulation later on.
Now, let's do toe side-slipping and do Angulation pose.
As you can see, if you give Angulation, the edges will stand up a lot.
The board will stop naturally.
Now, when you go down like this,
you have to center your weight on the board to make sure that you go straight down.
Now heelside slipping
Same thing with the pelvic rotation.
Now, Angulation
Raise your left shoulder.
Like this.
Because the edges stand like this,
The deck will naturally slow down.
Try practicing like this.
And if you're having a hard time practicing
because you're too fast in this slope,
or if you can't make one turn well,
you can use J-turn to make one turn each.
To draw an S, the first entry is very difficult.
So if you do J-turn, you can make the turn easier.
If you use this to practice
complete the S letter later, it will be easier for you to access more easily.
Let me show you J-Turn.
Go down there and lift the edge. J-Turn.
Now, make sure there's no one behind the slope.
J-turns can cause a lot of accidents.
Always first and second safety! Please be careful while riding.
Let me show you the heel-turn.
On riding flat
Heel
Now, if you separate the heel side and the toe side
and practice J-turn,
it will be very helpful in connecting the S later.
That is all.
Did you enjoy the demonstration video?
I'm sure you've been practicing basic carving a lot.
Basic carving is, in a way, a practice method for high-quality heel-turns,
Angulation is a practice method for good quality toe-turn.
Usually, beginners...
Self-taught riders often make turns with their pelvis sticking out of their axes
LG: what is the exact difference of good pelvis protrude and bad pelvis protrude?
because they want to touch their hands on the ground after watching videos.
In this case, the edges don't stand properly than the axis you're currently using,
so turns are easy to break.
That often leads to major accidents
when you meet a lot of muggles or go to expert slope.
For example, with your hips pulled out
and your legs bent like this,
your upper body is twisted straight ahead,
hitting your head against the slope, leading to a major accident.
So, for your safety,
I hope you practice your Angulation posture a lot and practice it with good balance.